[Intro: Beyoncé]
Oh na na na
Oh na na na
Oh na na na
Don't hurt yourself
Don't hurt yourself

[Verse 1: Beyoncé]
Who the fuck do you think I is?
You ain't married to no average bitch, boy
You can watch my fat ass twist, boy
As I bounce to the next dick, boy
And keep your money, I got my own
Keep a bigger smile on my face being alone
Bad motherfucker, God complex
Motivate your ass, call me Malcolm X
Yo operator, or innovator
Fuck you, hater, you can't recreate her, no, nuh-uh
You'll never recreate her, no, hell no

[Pre-Chorus 1: Beyoncé]
We just got to let it be
Let it be, let it be, let it be, baby
You just got to let it be
Let it be, let it be, let it be, babe
You might also like
Hold Up
Beyoncé
Sorry
Beyoncé
Pray You Catch Me
Beyoncé
[Chorus: Jack White]
When you hurt me, you hurt yourself
Don't hurt yourself
When you diss me, you diss yourself
Don't hurt yourself
When you hurt me, you hurt yourself
Don't hurt yourself (Don't hurt yourself)
Don't hurt yourself
When you love me, you love yourself
Love God herself

[Verse 2: Beyoncé]
I am the dragon breathing fire
Beautiful mane, I'm the lion
Beautiful man, I know you're lying
I am not broken, I'm not crying, I'm not crying
You ain't trying hard enough
You ain't loving hard enough
You don't love me deep enough
We not reaching peaks enough
Blindly in love, I fucks with you
'Til I realize I'm just too much for you
I'm just too much for you

[Pre-Chorus 2: Beyoncé]
You just got to let it be
Let it be, let it be, let it be, baby
Hey baby, who the fuck do you think I is?
I smell that fragrance on your Louis knit, boy
Just give my fat ass a big kiss, boy
Tonight I'm fucking up all your shit, boy
[Chorus: Beyoncé & Jack White]
When you hurt me, you hurt yourself
Try not to hurt yourself
When you play me, you play yourself
Don't play yourself
When you lie to me, you lie to yourself
You only lying to yourself (Don't hurt yourself)
When you love me, you love yourself
Love God herself

[Outro: Beyoncé]
We just got to let it be
Let it be, let it be, let it be, let it be, babe
Uh, this is your final warning (Don't hurt yourself)
You know I give you life (Don't hurt yourself)
If you try this shit again (Don't hurt yourself)
You gon' lose your wife